["You're The One" playing]
♪ I want you to want me ♪
[woman] Lex is like the Asian James Dean.
He is the white T-shirt-wearing,
tattooed, black jeans, earrings.
He is incredibly creative,
and he is everything that I would look at
if he was coming down the street.
♪ You know I want you, baby ♪
♪ You know I do ♪
[woman] Lex is pretty guarded,
but when he falls for somebody,
he falls pretty hard.
♪ 'Cause I do it for the thrill ♪
♪ For the rush ♪
♪ I do it for the pain... ♪
[woman] Outwardly, Lex is very tough.
Um, even in his appearance,
but he is incredibly sensitive
and emotional.
♪ Baby, you're the one ♪
♪ You're the one ♪
Cory?
-No, sorry.
-Fuck!
Sorry!
[chuckles]
♪ You're the one ♪
[man] Hey.
-Cory? Hey.
-I'm Cory.
-Good to see you. How's it going?
-Nice to meet you.
-Lex, right?
-Yeah.
-How's it going?
-You know.
So... um...
-So, have you been here before?
-No, I haven't. Have you?
No. Want to hop inside
and grab a drink?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
[Lex] How'd you get those jeans on?
[Mic] I know. I always wonder.
-Do you baby-powder first?
-Oh, no.
How are you gonna get them off later?
Well, there's a trick to do it.
I'm sure there is.
-Um...
-[both laugh]
That is a jacket!
Yeah. No, I got it, um,
like seven months ago.
-Yeah.
-And I waited until it was on sale.
I love a good mermaid fabric.
And we're 'stache bros over here.
-Oh, yeah. That's right.
-That's hilarious.
-You have a 'stache too.
-But I don't wax mine.
-Do you wax yours?
-Yeah.
I started, like... This is, like,
about a year-and-a-half old.
-Okay.
-This mustache.
I just always like to change my look up.
-Yeah.
-So I was just like--
Hence the reversible sequins.
[laughs]
Exactly.
I get bored too quickly.
You look like you have
a blue ox parked outside.
-I... You know, my Wisconsin roots.
-Do you get that a lot?
-You're from Wisconsin?
-Grew up in Wisconsin.
-How about you?
-Midwest boy.
-I am.
-Um, Southern California.
-I've been in New York for 18 years now.
-Okay.
So, do you blind date often?
I actually have not been on a blind date.
I like it more if it happens organically.
But I haven't been, like, on a real date,
like, in a long time.
I don't think I've ever been on a true,
actual blind date.
-Here's to first blind dates.
-Woo!
I think the thing is,
I've been set up before.
So it's kind of a blind date, right?
Like, you've never met them. But...
-there's a friend, an introduction--
-'Cause, like, "This is Jon."
There's that crazy Internet search,
where you find out everything you can.
-Creepy?
-A little creepy, but you know.
-Do you do the stalking?
-Yeah, I kind of do this.
So actually, funny story,
I had to stop using Tinder.
Um, because I did way too much stalking.
We're chatting,
"What do you do for work?" Meanwhile,
I knew their employment history,
'cause I had already found
all of that information out.
You're so cute for a creepy person.
-Uh, so what do you do?
-I'm a production designer.
So I design scenery
and costumes for theater.
Oh, nice.
I came to New York to be an actor.
Get the fuck out!
-Yes.
-Wait, did you go to school for acting?
I did. I went to school. Uh, I was trained
classically as an actor,
but I never really did that.
Okay. Why not?
Um, I mostly did musicals.
I grew up singing. Like, that's my thing.
Does... Do you, like, turn everything
into a song?
-Uh, when appropriate.
-Or when no one's looking.
-Right, right.
-[laughs]
-[Lex] So, um, what about you?
What do you do for work?
-Um, I work in real estate development.
-Oh, shit. That's fun.
I used to run a business called Moviefone.
Get the fuck out! Really?
Yeah.
Basically, I'm in fashion.
Good for you.
I don't know, maybe because I'm Italian
or something, but I love fashion.
-I'm a songwriter.
-Oh, you're a songwriter?
Yeah. But I also dog-walk.
I do, like, a bunch of things,
manage social media.
Anyway, I'm, like, digressing.
Recently, we sold Moviefone to MoviePass--
Right. See this empty finger?
[Brad laughs]
Too forward, Lex.
I can read you...
one of my...
songs.
By all means.
"I thought this would be the summer
that I would sink
Because I was barely making enough
for one soul
But God sent me a job to save my wings
And now I'm raking in more cash
than the leaves of fall"
Uh, so, I did a show called Seussical.
-"Oh, all the things you can think."
-"Oh, the thinks you can think," yes.
-So, who did you get to play?
-I was Wickersham. A Wickersham brother.
Okay. So you played a monkey.
I did. I'm impressed.
-Are you?
-Yes, yes.
First came out to my parents at...
I want to say 23.
I should know that date better, but, um,
going through every conversation,
every way my parents could react,
-and I was convinced, like--
-It was gonna be bad.
You know, Dad was gonna be like,
"Get the fuck out."
Like, I was petrified.
But, you know, I was like,
"I'm gonna do this.
I'm gonna come out,"
'cause I just felt so alone and, like...
So, finally, I just, like,
blurted it out at them
at the dinner table.
And they were both like...
-"And?"
-"Okay."
And my dad was like,
"Should we open a bottle of Maker's Mark?"
-What?
-So it's great.
That is the best thing
I think that I could have ever heard.
-It went well.
-Yeah.
How about you?
Um, similar.
On the phone with a much older boyfriend.
He was like, "Hey, so, I can't, um,
keep coming over to your house
and, like, telling your mom
that I'm your math tutor..."
-Oh, yeah.
-"...'cause I'm terrible at math,
and... it's a lie."
I was like, "Okay, hold on."
I went to the kitchen. I was like,
"Mom, remember when you used to ask me
every Saturday during breakfast
if I was into boys or girls?"
And she was like, "I know."
And I was like, "Yeah."
And she goes, "Go set the table."
-I was like, "Oh, okay."
-That's really sweet.
So it was fine. No, but I...
I feel very lucky.
"I'm ready to blow my load
I'm ready to spend money on everything
I'm ready for the summer of sin
I see the Versace jeans
across my wet dreams
And feel the soothing, sweet touch
of erotic massage
I'm gonna dive hard with lust in my hand
Hand on my heart
Watch out, my friends
I'm rising the charts"
And then it's the same...
basically, the same thing.
What do you think?
Um...
It depends on the situation.
I'm very comfortable
being in the background.
You know. I mean, it's what I do for work.
-Um--
-Which is not usual for creative people.
-The... the thing...
-'Cause they're very much prima donnas.
Yeah, but the thing that I put forward
is my work, right? It's not me.
And, like, I kind of... I have
a real problem with people who...
who... are prima donnas.
Don't get me wrong.
-Are you saying I'm a prima donna?
-She can be a prima donna.
-I'm sure she can.
-Yes, she can.
I think that might be the first time
I've ever used a female pronoun
in reference to myself.
-[Mic laughs] I do it all the time.
-That kind of felt really good, actually.
It was kind of empowering.
It's proud, you know. We're proud of this.
Yeah. Yeah.
[chuckles]
-Hi, guys. Um, your table is ready.
-[Lex] Hi.
-You can follow me. And grab your drinks.
-[Lex] Fantastic.
-[Mic] After you.
-[Lex] Oh. All right.
[woman] Right this way.
So, how long did you say
you played a monkey for?
-[laughs] Uh, six months, just about.
-Uh-huh.
-[woman] Here's the menus.
-Thanks. And that was fun?
Yes, it was a very good time.
Have you ever gone on a date with somebody
and ended up
not dating them, but walking their dog?
I actually ended up meeting this guy.
I told him I was a dog walker.
At first, he was like,
"Oh, let's hook up."
And then he was like, um...
'Cause I kept blowing him off, 'cause
I was really focusing on a job,
-but I think he--
-"Why blow him off when I can blow him?"
Yeah, exactly.
So he was... he was like...
"I'll let you fuck me
if you walk my dog."
And I'm like, "How about no? How about
I just fuck you,
and then you pay me to walk your dog?"
And then, eventually, we ended up
having sex anyway,
but... where, like,
there was no, like, barter of goods.
But did you ever walk his dog?
No.
So, when did you decide you were a gaymo?
Yeah, I was... I was a sophomore in...
in college. And--
I bet you were so cute
as a sophomore in college.
Um, I had studied religion.
I had taken a lot of classes.
I, like, wanted to be...
I wanted to work in ministry.
-Okay.
-And I just kind of had a crisis of faith.
So, did you've to decide where you're
like, "Oh, I kind of want to be a pastor,
but, like, I kind of want to suck dick"?
Uh, yeah, that was problematic.
I thought that
I had some sort of affliction...
-Uh-huh.
-...that God was going to heal me of,
and I was just gonna
figure it out one day.
That's the first time I ever let myself
deal with the fact that I might...
be gay.
You know, that I might have this identity.
That's really, um...
I didn't... absolutely didn't expect that.
-Yeah.
-I grew up, um...
not that religious. I mean, kind of.
But I knew at a very young age,
regardless of religion,
that, like...
loving somebody of the same gender
could never be a bad thing.
Wow.
So, you... do you have siblings?
Yes, one older brother.
-Okay.
-[Brad] He's twenty...
twenty months older than me, I think.
It's really tight. 22 months. I just had
to do math in my head. That was tough.
I'm the youngest of four.
The little prince in the family.
I've two older half siblings: an older
half brother and older half sister.
He had twins recently.
-So you're a "guncle"?
-I'm a "guncle."
I am. My sister has a son,
a five-year-old boy.
He's... everything.
And they actually call me guncle,
-which is really cute.
-Oh. That's sweet.
-I have two lady nieces.
-Oh, really?
They're total terrors,
but they're delightful.
-So, I used to play football.
-Like, in college?
Uh, played in college,
and then briefly, uh,
had a cup of coffee
with the Arizona Cardinals, so...
-What?
-Yeah, it was--
So you're technically, like...
a pro-football player.
Was. Still not doing it, but, yeah.
But, but... Okay.
You realize you're every homosexual's
wet dream, right?
You just like...
the long hair and the helmet and the pads.
Um, that's fun.
But... I don't watch football anymore.
I've...
-You don't?
-No, not at all.
-Okay. We have that in common. Cheers.
-Cheers. We...
-Perfect.
-Fuck football.
Fuck football. I play rugby still.
So I've got a bunch of things wrong
with my body.
Will you excuse me as I adjust the things
that are wrong with my pants right now?
[woman] Guys.
-Thank you very much.
-[woman] Salmon.
-[woman] Duck.
-[Lex] Oh, shit, you win.
-I've got brussels sprouts with this.
-[Lex] And you've got sprouts.
-You want to share some?
-Yes, I do.
I have definitely wandering fork syndrome.
-[woman] Salmons.
-Awesome. This looks amazing.
I don't know how to do this.
Yes, you do.
You pick up your fork and knife.
[chuckles]
-[woman] Enjoy.
-Cheers.
Cheers.
[clink]
[Mic] Living in New York City...
it's just like, you know, we can
experience everything and anything, so--
Have you experienced
everything and everything?
Let me put it this way.
[in Italian] Top or...bottom?
I only experience once,
-if that's what you mean.
-You experienced one?
-Yeah. I only like one side.
-Can I guess?
-I'm sure you know.
-[in Italian] Bottom?
No.
Mmm!
[chuckles]
So... [in Italian] top.
Let's change topic here.
Why not? Why?
Does that make you uncomfortable?
I feel like as a first date,
we can skip on that conversation.
Doesn't that inform a second date?
Second date, we can talk about it.
Okay.
So, how is your dating life?
Nonexistent.
Mmm!
-Oh, no.
-But my hookup life--
-Why is that?
-My hookup life is existent,
but it's not too existent.
Um...
Why is that?
Well...
I feel like, you know,
you being gay as well,
everyone just wants to have sex.
And...
they... you know, they like the idea
of a relationship,
but, then, when it comes
to actually dating, no one wants to date.
I almost feel like I'm kind of
a piece of meat,
-they only see me--
-I don't see you as a piece of meat.
[laughs] Well, thank you.
So...
why are you single right now?
[Lex] Uh, hmm.
Well... [clears throat]
...could be because of work. Um...
One of the reasons is sort of practical.
I'm out of town a lot for work.
And so it's sort of hard to...
I mean, you know what it's like.
You'll meet somebody...
and...
there is this sense of, like,
not good enough.
-Hmm.
-[Lex] Right?
Whether that is, like you're not...
athletic enough,
you're not...
white enough,
you happen to be
a subcategory of a minority.
Okay.
-As a gaysian.
-[chuckling] Okay.
But, like, I'm not gonna pine over someone
who's not interested in me,
because, like... it's just not...
worth it.
And I don't want to be some version of me
that other people want...
me to be.
I don't know. I sort of, for a long time,
I've been, like, turned off to dating.
I think gay men have a case of what
I like to call "next best thing-itis."
So it's just a function of where...
they'll like, "Oh, yeah.
Like, you're fun for now.
You check a couple boxes for now.
But I'm gonna, like, always keep my eye
open for, like, the next best thing."
-Yes.
-Right?
-Which, like...
-You're so true.
-...I don't have any patience for.
-Right. Am I your best?
[Lex laughs]
Oh, you do have a very confident cannoli,
don't you?
[chuckles] Yeah. Love that.
Um, eventually, I do want to have a...
-[no dialog]
-a partner and kids.
Oh.
But...
my main goal is...
I'm focusing on my song... songwriting.
Yeah, so...
if a relationship happens,
a relationship happens.
And... if it doesn't, then...
-you know, whatever.
-Right.
-I'll just wait.
The waiting game.
Yeah.
Wait. So, you're a gaysian.
-I am, as are you.
-I am.
-Yes.
-Do you suffer from the glow?
I do. Do you?
The Asian flush.
It's like a chemical thing.
I'm pretty sure it's an enzyme.
And my brother told me...
I guess I was probably like 18 or 19,
"Are you taking your Pepcid AC?"
I was like, "What?"
And he was like, "You gotta take your
Pepcid AC or you're gonna turn red."
I was like, "I am turning red."
He said, "That's how you stop it."
And I was like, "All right."
And to this day,
if I know I'm gonna be doing
any sort of drinking,
yes, Pepcid AC is always
before I leave the house.
Did you take one today?
-I did take one today, but, uh--
-Ah.
-Do you want to grab another drink?
-Yeah. I might switch it up.
-I might get a different drink.
-All right. Great.
[Mic sighs]
[Lex] Did you get your purse?
-I did.
-Great.
-Always with me.
-First, first.
[Lex] When you were a football player,
did you have long hair?
Yeah. I grew it out, and it was just
these, like, beautiful, luscious locks.
Wait. Is it beautiful, luscious locks now?
I... I think that they look great.
They have a little ways to go.
-You want to see?
-I do.
I'll just pull it out. It's all tied up.
We got it out. It's--
Wait. Hang on here.
-It's not--
-Wait.
I have such hair envy.
[Brad chuckles]
[Peter] A lot of my friends
that are in the dating scene,
like, have, like their go-to things
that they do.
Like there's always the same restaurant
that they go to or--
How boring.
-Kind of, right?
-Yeah.
Um, I mean, for a while,
I was in that rut as well.
Somewhere,
I got self-conscious of that.
I bet you these servers just think
I'm a big, old ho, so...
-They probably do.
-I mean, I'm okay with that.
-But they... they probably are as well.
-[laughs]
So...
[Lex] Have you ever felt, like,
heartbroken by a breakup?
Yes. I feel like, you know,
it really hurt me.
Um, in the end, it was more my call.
What about you? Like, did you...
I'm sure you experienced the same, right?
Yeah. No, I've experienced
a lot of heartbreak, I think.
Because I think it's hard to find...
a connection with people and I think that
once you do find that connection,
you have to make yourself vulnerable.
And that's not something
that I normally do.
-You've probably found out that like...
-Right.
I'm quick to make jokes, right?
Yeah. Oh, I got that.
-Yeah, totally.
-And it... If I do that,
it means that I'm protected.
And if I'm protected, like,
you can't hurt me.
You feel like, you know,
you're in your comfort zone.
Right.
[Lex] Well, this was fun.
-[Lex] I'd love to hang out again.
-[Mic] We should.
[Lex] Yeah.
[Jonathan]
What you doing next weekend?
[Lex] Um...
Next weekend, I'm out of town.
So, you come here often?
-I've been here a few times.
-Okay.
Hi.
Can I get a...
just a bourbon on the rocks?
[woman] For you?
-Glenfiddich 15.
-[woman] Glenfiddich?
[woman] Okay.
Scotch.
Does that put you to sleep?
[Lex chuckles]
-You trying to put me to sleep?
-[Cory laughs]
It's a great end to the date, right?
-Cheers.
To sleepy time.
[both chuckle]
I feel like you have a drag name.
-Uh, I might dabble in the drag arts.
-Oh, shit.
-Yeah?
-Her name is Queer Wang.
-Queer Wang.
-She's a lovely, lovely lady.
You got pictures?
I have... I have a few.
I have a couple.
-That's a pretty good one of her.
-Oh, shit. Hey, Queera.
[Peter laughs]
-[Peter] She is pretty.
-[Lex] Black magic!
[Peter] I know.
-[Brad] I've only done drag once.
-Okay.
But people are caught off-guard
by my collection of heels or...
the three wigs that are hanging
on the wall for no reason.
Wait, but that's...
perfect. I mean, like, that...
The balance is what counts,
I think, right?
I'm a butch queen at heart, so--
Wait. That's fantastic.
-[Lex] I have a drag name.
-What is it?
It's, uh, Contasia Bamboo.
Contasia Bamboo.
Does that connect to your... your
stereotypical bamboo tattoo over here?
Oh, wow. You just called
my bamboo tattoo stereotypical.
You're a cunt.
-Do you have tattoos?
-No. I have no threshold for pain.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah.
How'd you get rid of your unibrow?
So rude. [laughing]
Do people go on dates with you
like, "Oh, yeah, like, big 6 ft. 4?"
Six foot-four, yeah.
"You know, size 14 shoe.
Big, scruffy rugby dude.
Like...
he's gonna be a beast and, like...
fuck the hell out of me in the bedroom"?
And then they see the heels
and they're just like, "Hold up."
-I mean, the heels--
-Are there expectations?
I think people probably have expectations.
And it sounds like you're more of a, like,
"Listen, whatever I can do to you,
you can do to me" type of person?
Mmm... I'd say I'm... I'm very dominant
in most situations.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
-Wow.
-I'm very driven by being told, like,
"No, you can't do this"--
I don't think
we should have a second date.
Well, challenge accepted.
Oh, okay.
-I really enjoyed my first blind date.
-[Cory] Yeah?
Were you nervous at all?
Mmm...
no.
It is kind of exciting, right,
to meet a complete stranger?
-Totally.
-Yeah.
Yeah, I feel like a lot of people...
do that for different reasons online.
[both laughing]
True. Ours are quite innocent
by comparison.
I'm... I'm really glad that my first blind
date wasn't blindfolded ass-up.
'Cause that would be awkward.
-Do you want to share a Lyft home?
-Yeah.
Well, um...
Yeah, maybe we should get out of here.
Let's go. After you.
Oh, shit. Okay.
Do you mind making the air, like,
a little lower, please?
Well, um...
I feel like I should get your number.
Okay.
-Right?
-Yeah.
'Cause, like...
Gotta get my phone out.
Here.
We never even did last names, right?
No, because I know exactly what's gonna
happen if I give you my last name.
[Cory chuckles]
'Cause I was doing most of the talking,
I felt that you weren't that into me.
So, I want to know
if you're interested in, like...
meeting, like, for another date?
Um...
I don't know about another date,
-but I would definitely be interested in--
-Friendship?
-Yeah.
-No, that's great.
[Lex] Let's do it.
-Pleasure to meet you, Peter.
-Likewise. Let's do this again soon.
-Yeah. For sure. Good night.
-You too.
[Jonathan] I can't open this door.
This almost looks like an ashtray,
the way it's set up.
But it's actually the handle of the door.
Good night. Thanks.
-So, this is my stop.
-All right, Brad.
-[Lex] Hope to see you soon?
-Absolutely.
Okay. Let's make it happen.
You'll text or call?
-I will.
-All right.
-[Cory] I had a really good time.
-Me too.
-Goodnight.
-Okay. Have a good night.
[Cory] Bye.
[sighs]
[sighs wearily]
["Reunion" playing]
♪ You came out of nowhere ♪
♪ Stealing my heart and brain ♪
♪ Flaming my every cell ♪
[man] Hi.
Hey.
-How're you doing?
-How are you, Daddy Longlegs?
-[Cory] Good to see you.
-Good to see you too.
-Ooh, it's warm today.
-I know.
Do you have high heels on your shirt?
I do. I mean, I figure if I'm gonna go
on a date with a baby giraffe,
-I should wear my heels.
-[Cory laughs]
No, you look good.
-I'm glad you came.
-Well, that's really good to hear.
-Um, if you want to go in, I have tickets.
-Let's do it.
[Lex] So...
did you stalk me?
I didn't yet.
-You didn't? Really?
-I didn't.
[Cory] Um, I don't know your last name.
[Lex] Oh.